thinkenergygroup.com 2001-12-05

# Technical Staffing - Press Release - Atlanta, Georgia, Florida

| 

**Privacy/Security**

**Information You Provide**

At ThinkJobs.com, we respect your privacy. Our job-seeker registration form requires users to submit contact information (such as their e-mail address) and to complete a candidate profile containing information about employment preferences and qualifications. Job seekers may also submit a resume. The user's contact and personal information is used to contact them when necessary, and to send automatic notifications of matching job opportunities or confidential "invitations" that may result when employers search the ThinkJobs.com database. When potential employers search our candidate database, they are not searching user resumes. Rather, they peruse profiles created by users. The profile created by the job seeker is designed to protect his/her privacy and does not contain any personally identifiable information UNLESS the candidate enters such information intentionally.E-mail addresses submitted to ThinkJobs.com will be used only for the purposes of the ThinkJobs.com career search service. As stated above, the release of a user's resume, contact information and e-mail are under the control of the user and will not be released unless so authorized by the user in one of the ways outlined above, or if the user specifically chooses to receive updates and special offers from ThinkJobs.com. User contact information is used only for delivering ThinkJobs.com services and are kept confidential. This information will never be sold or otherwise distributed to third parties for purposes other than those outlined above. We have taken measures to assure both the physical and electronic security of the data we store. 

**IP Addresses**

We store IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable.

**Cookies**

Our site uses cookies to optimize service for visitors. A cookie lets us recognize repeat visitors more quickly and makes visits to our site more personalized and productive.

**Outside Links**

This site contains links to other sites. ThinkJobs.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites and can only recommend caution in using such sites.

**Private E-mail**

ThinkJobs.com strongly encourages users who do not wish to receive employment-related information at their primary e-mail address (e.g. place of work) to open a personal e-mail account at any of the many sites offering free Internet e-mail accounts, such as hotmail.com, yahoo.com and mail.com. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**

This site gives users the option of removing their information from our database, to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. You can send e-mail to [support@ThinkJobs.com](mailto:Support@ThinkJobs.com).

**Security**

ThinkJobs.com takes every precaution to protect user information. When a user submits sensitive information via the Web site, that information is protected both online and off-line. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect your information off-line. All user information is restricted in our offices, not just the sensitive information to which we refer above. Only employees who need the information to perform their job (for example, a billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to that information. Furthermore, all employees are kept up-to-date on ThinkJobs.com's security and privacy practices. Our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place upon privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected.Finally, the servers where we store personal information are kept in a protected environment, with multiple, redundant security features.If you have any questions about the security at ThinkJobs.com, please don't hesitate to contact us at: [support@ThinkJobs.com](mailto:Support@ThinkJobs.com).

**Change/Modify**

This site gives users the option of changing and modifying information previously provided. Simply go to [www.ThinkJobs.com](http://www.thinkjobs.com/), click on the Your Account link and enter your Username and Password. From Your Account, select the appropriate link to edit your profile or contact information or submit an updated resume.

**Notification of Changes**

This policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the Web site. Changes will be prominently posted. ThinkJobs.com visitors will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. Please check this site regularly for information about revisions to our privacy policy. 

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [webmaster@thinkjobsobs.com](mailto:Webmaster@ThinkJobs.com).
